Boyars mss., 1960-2010 LMC 2953
Lilly Library
- Publishing Files
  - Parsipur, Shahrnush
    - Touba & the Meaning of Night - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Touba & the Meaning of Night - reviews, 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Peterkiewicz, Jerzy
    - Author file, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - In the Scales of Fate - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
  - Phillips, Delores
    - The Darkest Child - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - The Darkest Child - reviews, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Pilhes, Rene Victor
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Potter, Lawrence
    - Mathematics Minus Fear - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - This May Help You Understand the World Better - reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Photographs, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Preez, Peter du
    - Genocide - reviews, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Price, Christopher
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - The Confait Confessions - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Prima, Diane di
    - Memoirs of a Beatnik - correspondence and files, 1994-2002 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Memoirs of a Beatnik - reviews, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Memoirs of a Beatnik - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Prone, Terry
    - The Scattering of Mrs. Blake and Related Matters - reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - The Scattering of Mrs. Blake and Related Matters - correspondence and files, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Just A Few Words - reviews, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Puech, Bernard
    - Sous l'Etoile du Chien - reviews and publicity, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Pujade-Renaud, Claude
    - Belle Mere - reviews, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Quin, Ann
    - Berg - correspondence and files, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Berg - typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Passages - reviews, 1969-1981 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Passages - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Reviews, 1989? (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Author file, 1976-1993 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Radiguet, Raymond
    - The Devil in the Flesh - correspondence and files, 1986-2005 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - The Devil in the Flesh - cover proofs, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - The Devil in the Flesh - reviews, 1997-2005 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - The Devil in the Flesh - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Count d'Orgel - correspondence and files, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Count d'Orgel - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Raphael, Lev
    - Author file, 1991-2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Rasp, Renate
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Reavey, George
    - The New Russian Poets - correspondence and files, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Rebello, Stephen
    - Alfred Hitchcock - cover proofs, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Alfred Hitchcock - reviews, 1990-1999 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Alfred Hitchcock - typescript, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 16-18)
  - Reyes, Alina
    - Author file, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Ritchie, Paul
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Confessions of a People Lover - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Riverbend
    - Baghdad Burning - reviews and publicity, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 22-24)
    - Baghdad Burning - cover proofs, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Robertson, James
    - Profit or People? - reviews, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Power, Money and Sex - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Roche, Henri-Pierre
    - Jules et Jim - reviews, 1993-1998 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Jules et Jim - cover proofs, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Jules et Jim - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Rodriguez, Luis J.
    - Always Running - reviews, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Always Running - cover proofs, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Always Running - cover drafts and artwork, undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Always Running - correspondence and files, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Always Running - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Roe, Sue; Susan Sellers, Nicole Ward Jouve & Michele Roberts
    - The Semi-Transparent Envelope - reviews, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - The Semi-Transparent Envelope - correspondence and files, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - The Semi-Transparent Envelope - cover proofs, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Rogers, Paul T.
    - Saul's Book - page proofs, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Saul's Book - correspondence and files, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Publicity regarding murder, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Rosen, Charles
    - Schoenberg - correspondence and files, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Schoenberg - reviews, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Schoenberg - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
  - Roshchin, Mikhail
    - First Love - reviews, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - First Love - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Rozewicz, Tadeusz
    - Witnesses - reviews, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Mariage Blanc - reviews, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Mariage Blanc - cover proofs, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Reading the Apocalypse in Bed - reviews, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Reading the Apocalypse in Bed - page proofs, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Reading the Apocalypse in Bed - correspondence and files, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Reading the Apocalypse in Bed - cover proofs, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Rubinstein, Renate
    - Take It & Leave It - corrected page proofs (multiple copies), undated (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
    - Take It & Leave It - typescript and page proofs, 1987? (Box 27, Folder 21-24)
    - Take It & Leave It - reviews, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Take It & Leave It - correspondence and files, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Take It & Leave It - cover layouts, undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Samuel, Claude
    - Prokofiev - page proofs, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Sandblom, Philip
    - Creativity & Disease - correspondence and files, 1991-2000 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
      Includes floppy disc
    - Creativity & Disease - reviews, 1985-2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Author file, 1992-1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Sandford, Jeremy
    - Smiling David - corresondence and files, 1971-1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Smiling David - reviews, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Smiling David - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Edna the Inebriate Woman - artwork, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Edna the Inebriate Woman - correspondence and files, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Edna the Inebriate Woman - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Virgin of the Clearways - correspondence and files, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Cathy Come Home - cover proofs, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Cathy Come Home - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Saumont, Annie
    - I'm No Truck - cover drafts and artwork, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - I'm No Truck - reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - I'm No Truck - correspondence and files of translator Cynthia Liebow, 1990-1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - I'm No Truck - typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - I'm No Truck - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Schlesinger, Philip
    - Televising Terrorism - reviews, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Schmidt, Arno
    - The Egghead Republic - correspondence and files, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - The Egghead Republic - cover proofs, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - The Egghead Republic - reviews, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - The Egghead Republic - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Scenes from the Life of a Faun - cover proofs, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Scenes from the Life of a Faun - correspondence and files, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Scenes from the Life of a Faun - cover drafts, undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Scenes from the Life of a Faun - reviews, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Scenes from the Life of a Faun - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Abend Mit Goldrend - correspondence and files, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and files of editor Ernst Krawehl, 1975-1990 (Box 28, Folder 28-31)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Evening Edged in Gold - reviews, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Evening Edged in Gold - correspondence and files, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence regarding "the Arno Schmidt problem", 1981-1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Schoenberg, A.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Schonzeler, Hans-Hubert
    - Dvorak - correspondence and files, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Dvorak - reviews, 1984-1997 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Dvorak - photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Furtwangler - correspondence and files, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Author file, 1982-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Schrag, Peter
    - Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Schreiner, Claus
    - Musica Brasileira - cover proofs, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Author file, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Schwartz, Gary
    - Bets & Scams - reviews, 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Bets & Scams - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Selby Jr., Hubert
    - Requiem for a Dream - correspondence and files, 1979-2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Requiem for a Dream - film materials, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Requiem for a Dream - reviews, 1996-2001 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Requiem for a Dream - cover proofs, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Requiem for a Dream - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - The Room - correspondence and files, 1989-2002 (Box 29, Folder 18-19)
    - The Room - reviews, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - The Room - cover proofs, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - The Room - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - The Willow Tree - correspondence and files, 1997-1999 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - The Willow Tree - reviews, 1997-2008 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Song of the Silent Snow - reviews, 1986-2007 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Song of the Silent Snow - cover proofs, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Song of the Silent Snow - correspondence and files, 1986-1999 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Song of the Silent Snow - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Awake - typescript, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - The Demon - correspondence and files, 1978-1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - The Demon - cover drafts, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - The Demon - cover proofs, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - The Demon - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Waiting Period - reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Waiting Period - correspondence and files, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Waiting Period - cover proofs, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Waiting Period - typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 3-5)
    - Last Exit to Brooklyn - reviews, 1967-1991 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
    - Last Exit to Brooklyn - cover proofs, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Last Exit to Brooklyn - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1986-2005 (Box 30, Folder 9-13)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Reviews, 1999-2004 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Searle, Chris
    - The New Season - correspondence and files, 1975-1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - The New Season - reviews, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Mainland - reviews, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Author file, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Segovia, Andres
    - Segovia: An Autobiography - correspondence and files, 1977-1981 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Segovia: An Autobiography - cover proofs, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Segovia: An Autobiography - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Senator, Ronald
    - Requiem Letters - reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Requiem Letters - correspondence and files, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Requiem Letters - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, 1968? (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Shafak, Elif
    - The Gaze - reviews, 2004-2006 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - The Gaze - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Flea Palace - reviews, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - The Flea Palace - correspondence and files, 1995-2006 (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
    - The Flea Palace - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - The Flea Palace - London-Brighton tour, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Reviews and publicity, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Author file, 2001-2008 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Shaffer, Anthony
    - Murderer - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Sleuth - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Sleuth - reviews, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Shaiken, Harley
    - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Shepard, Jim
    - Writers at the Movies - reviews, 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Shukshin, Vasily
    - Roubles & Kopeks - correspondence and files, 1984-1994 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Roubles & Kopeks - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Roubles & Kopeks - cover drafts and artwork, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Roubles & Kopeks - reviews, 1985-1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Roubles & Kopeks - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Author file, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Shuttle, Penelope
    - Wailing Monkey Embracing a Tree - reviews, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Wailing Monkey Embracing a Tree - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - All the Usual Hours of Sleeping - correspondence and files, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - All the Usual Hours of Sleeping - reviews, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - All the Usual Hours of Sleeping - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - The Wise Wound - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Rainsplitter in the Zodiac Garden - reviews, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Rainsplitter in the Zodiac Garden - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1976-2001 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Shvarts, Yevgheny
    - The Naked King - correspondence and files, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - The Naked King - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Silverstein, Shel
    - Runny Babbit - correspondence and files, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Runny Babbit - cover proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - A Light in the Attic - correspondence and files, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Simon, Claude
    - Lecon de Choses - reviews, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Skelton, Geoffrey
    - Author file, 1971-2002 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Skiles, Don
    - Miss America - reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Skolimowski, Henryk
    - Eco-Philosophy - cover drafts and proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Eco-Philosophy - correspondence and files, 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Eco-Philosophy - page proofs, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Eco-Philosophy - reviews, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Eco-Philosophy - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Skwara, E. W.
    - The Plague in Siena - typescript, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Smart, Ninian
    - Choosing a Faith - reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Author file, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Soderberg, Hjalmar
    - The Serious Game - reviews, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - The Serious Game - cover proofs, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert
    - Crystal Vision - reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Crystal Vision - correspondence and files, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Crystal Vision - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Aberration of Starlight - correspondence and files, 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Aberration of Starlight, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1981-1999 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Reviews, 1981-1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Southern, Terry
    - Blue Movie - reviews, 1973-1981 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Blue Movie - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1995-2009 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Spencer, Amy
    - DIY - reviews, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - The Crafter Culture Handbook - reviews, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Spiegl, Fritz
    - Lives, Wives, and Loves of the Great Composers - reviews, 1990-1997 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Lives, Wives, and Loves of the Great Composers - correspondence and files, 1990-1997 (Box 32, Folder 21-22)
  - Spiegelman, Katia
    - Soul Catcher - reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Soul Catcher - correspondence and files, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Soul Catcher - cover drafts, undated (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Author file, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Spurling, John
    - The British Empire (Part 1) - reviews, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - The British Empire - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Macrune's Guevara - reviews, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Shades of Heathcliff - cover proofs, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Shades of Heathcliff - correspondence and files, 1981-1994 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - In the Heart of the British Museum - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Stangerup, Henrik
    - Mother - correspondence and files, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - The Man Who Wanted to be Guilty - reviews, 1982-1991 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Snake in the Heart - correspondence and files, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Snake in the Heart - reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - The Seducer - cover drafts and artwork, undated (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - The Seducer - correspondence and files, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Daughter of - reviews, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - The Road to Lagoa Santa - reviews, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - The Road to Lagoa Santa - correspondence and files, 1983-1997 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
    - Brother Jacob - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Reviews, 1982-1998 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
    - Author file, 1995-2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Stockhausen, Karlheinz
    - Stockhausen on Music - reviews, 1988-1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Stockhausen on Music - cover proofs, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Robin Maconie author file, 1981-2009 (Box 33, Folder 10-12)
  - Storey, Anthony
    - Hale Mary - typescript, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
    - The Saviour - correspondence and files, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - The Saviour - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Brothers Keepers - reviews, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Brothers Keepers - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Graceless Go I - reviews, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Graceless Go I - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Platinum Jag - reviews, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Courage and Cowardice - typescript, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - The Centre Holds - reviews, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - The Centre Holds - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - The Rector - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Unknown typescript, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Author file, 1982-1998 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Stravinsky, Igor
    - An Autobiography - correspondence and files, 1976-1989 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - An Autobiography - reviews, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - An Autobiography - cover proofs, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - An Autobiography - cover drafts, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Szasz, Thomas S.
    - Ideology and Insanity - correspondence and files, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Szechter, Szymon
    - Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bridge on Ice - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Talese, Gay
    - The Kingdom and the Power - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
  - Tansi, Sony Labou
    - The Antipeople - cover proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - The Antipeople - reviews, 1988-1996 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - The Antipeople - cover drafts, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - The Antipeople - correspondence and files, 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - The Antipeople - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Tekin, Latife
    - Berji Kristen - cover proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Berji Kristen - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Swords of Ice - cover proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Dear Shameless Death - reviews, 2001-2009 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Dear Shameless Death - cover proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Reviews, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Texier, Catherine
    - Love Me Tender - cover drafts, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Love Me Tender - reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Love Me Tender - correspondence and files, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Author file, 1987-1998 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Tiger, Lionel
    - The Manufacture of Evil - reviews, 1992-1997 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - The Manufacture of Evil - correspondence and files, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - The Manufacture of Evil - cover drafts, undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Author file, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Tiger, Virginia
    - William Golding - reviews, 1975-2002 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - William Golding - correspondence and files, 1973-2004 (Box 34, Folder 28-29)
      Includes floppy discs (3)
    - Author file, 1980-2003 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Topor, Roland
    - Joko's Anniversary - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
  - Toussaint, Jean-Philippe
    - Monsieur - reviews, 1987-1992 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - The Bathroom - reviews, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - The Bathroom - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Reviews, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Author file, 1987-1993 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Turbina, Nika
    - First Draft - reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Tucker, Eva
    - Drowning - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Turner, John F. C.
    - Housing by People - reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Housing by People - cover proofs, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)